Guide to the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council, Seattle Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council Seattle records
1918-1972
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
1851
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America.$bDistrict Council (Seattle, Wash.).
9.21 cubic feet (9 boxes)
Administrative papers of a city-wide coordinating body for affiliated local unions
City-wide coordinating body for affiliated local unions. Along with the Carpenters and Joiners of America, the organizations included in this accession are the Central Labor Council of Seattle and Vicinity, Northwest Chapter of Associated General Contractors of America, Seattle Department of Lighting, and Washington State Council of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America.
Organized into 2 accessions.
Accession No. 1851-001, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council Seattle records, 1918-1972
Accession No. 1851-004, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council Seattle records, 1957-1969
Organizational features, correspondence, minutes, agreements, wage scales, financial records, by-laws, reports, conferences and conventions.
No restrictions on access.
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America$bDistrict Council (Seattle, Wash.)$vArchives; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Carpenters$xLabor unions$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor movement$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor union members$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor unions$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Business correspondence; By-laws; Ephemera; Maps; Records (Documents); Carr, Harry L.
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Washington (State); Seattle
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council Seattle records, 1918-1972; 1851-001; 8.21 cubic feet (8 boxes)
  Arranged in 19 series.
  SERIES I: CONSTITUTIONS AND BYLAWS, 1925-1965
  SERIES II: OFFICE FILES, 1929-1961
  SERIES III: CORRESPONDENCE, 1919-1972
  SERIES IV: MINUTES, 1922-1967
  SERIES V: AGREEMENTS, 1918-1971
  SERIES VI: TRADE RULES, 1936-1958
  SERIES VII: WAGE SCALES, 1928-1961
  SERIES VIII: PROPOSALS, 1961-1962
  SERIES IX: RESOLUTIONS, 1930-1971
  SERIES X: FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1924-1964
  SERIES XI: REPORTS, 1928-1970
  SERIES XII: LEGAL DOCUMENTS, 1944-1967
  SERIES XIII: LEGISLATION, 1934-1959
  SERIES XIV: COURT CASES, 1930-1940
  SERIES XV: CONFERENCES AND CONVENTIONS, 1928-1971
  SERIES XVI: NOTES, 1949-1955
  SERIES XVII: MAPS
  SERIES XVIII: CLIPPINGS, 1952-1968
  SERIES XIX: EPHEMERA, 1919-1961
  Organizational features, correspondence, minutes, agreements, wage scales, financial records, conferences and conventions.
  No restrictions on access.
  Donated by District Council, 9/10/1969.
  - CONSTITUTIONS AND BYLAWS, 1925-1965; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1, 8/1-8/3)
    - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of American District Council Seattle, 1943-1965; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, District Council and Affiliate Locals, 1943-1965 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Carpenters and Joiners of America Bylaws Committee, 1925-1961; Subseries B (Box-folder 8/1-8/2)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Bylaws Committee Part 1, 1925-1954 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Bylaws Committee Part 2, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Carpenter's Center, 1954; Subseries C (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Constitutions and Pay-Laws, 1954 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - OFFICE FILES, 1929-1961; SERIES II (Box-folder ½-1/3)
    - Insurance Policy, 1929-1933 (Box-folder ½)
    - Membership Cards and Addresses, 1948, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1919-1972; SERIES III (Box-folder 1/4-4/19)
    - Incoming Correspondence, 1919-1968; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/4-2/59)
      - Alaska Fisherman's Union, 1957 (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Alaska Industrial Board and Alaska Fisherman's Union, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - American Federation of Labor (AFL), 1924 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - AFL Building and Construction Trades Department, 1929-1937 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - AFL Maritime Trades Department Washington State Council, 1948 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - AFL Representative C.O. Young, 1932 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Associated General Contractors of America, 1948 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Associated General Contractors of America, Alaska Chapter, 1952 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Associated General Contractors of America, Mountain Pacific Chapter, 1947-1959 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Associated General Contractors of America, Seattle Chapter, 1923, 1934, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Seattle Union Record, Ault, E.B., 1927 (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Basset, Geisness and Vance, Cisco Construction Company Case, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 1/15)
      - Bissell, Morton, 1954 (Box-folder 1/16)
      - Baier, OW. M, Cisco Construction Co., 1954 (Box-folder 1/17)
      - United States Senate Committee on Naval Affairs, Bone, Homer T., 1935-1937 (Box-folder 1/18)
      - Boyd, R. Eugene, 1956 (Box-folder 1/19)
      - International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers of America, Local 142 (Seattle), 1936 (Box-folder ½0)
      - Bridge, Structural, Reinforcing Steel and Ornamental Ironworkers and Riggers Union, Local 86, 1929 (Box-folder ½1)
      - British Columbia Federationist, 1923 (Box-folder ½2)
      - International Broom and Whisk Makers Union, Boyer, Will R., 1935 (Box-folder ½3)
      - State Building Trades Council of California, 1927 (Box-folder ½4)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1924, 1936, 1950-1959 (Box-folder ½5)
      - California State Council of Carpenters, 1929-1932 (Box-folder ½6)
      - California State Carpenters and Joiners, State Millmen's Committee, 1934 (Box-folder ½7)
      - Bay Counties District Council of Carpenters, San Francisco, 1926-1934 (Box-folder ½8)
      - Fall City Carpenters' District Council, 1935 (Box-folder ½9)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Cosgrove, John T., First General Vice President, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 1/30)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Lakey, George H., Second General Vice President, 1926-1937 (Box-folder 1/31)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Stevenson, John R., First General Vice President, 1960 (Box-folder 1/32)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Muir, A.W., Member of the General Executive Board, 1930-1934 (Box-folder 1/33)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Hutcheson, M.A., General President, 1952-1965 (Box-folder 1/34)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Hutcheson, W.L., General President Part 1, 1919, 1926, 1947-1951 (Box-folder 1/35)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Hutcheson, W.L., General President Part 2, 1927-1933 (Box-folder 1/36)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Hutcheson, W.L., General President Part 3, 1933-1937 (Box-folder 1/37)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Dowler, P.W., General Representative and Hoard, Maurice, 1926-1930 (Box-folder 1/38)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Moody, Lawrence, General Representative, 1937 (Box-folder 1/39)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Duffy, Frank, General Secretary, 1923-1935 (Box-folder 1/40)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Neale, Thomas, General Treasurer, 1923-1930 (Box-folder 1/41)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Grand Rapids District Council, 1926 (Box-folder 1/42)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Grays Harbor District Council, 1929-1936 (Box-folder 1/43)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Ladies' Auxiliary 179, 1927-1929 (Box-folder 1/44)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Los Angeles District Council, 1926, 1937-1967 (Box-folder 1/45)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Montana State Council; Finlay, James B., Secretary-Treasurer, 1919 (Box-folder 1/46)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, New Orleans District Council, 1923 (Box-folder 1/47)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, New York District Council, 1958 (Box-folder 1/48)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, New York State Millman's Conference Committee; McNaughton, George F., Secretary, 1933 (Box-folder 1/49)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Oregon State Council, 1927-1929 (Box-folder 1/50)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Philadelphia District Council, 1928 (Box-folder 1/51)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Portland District Council, 1923,1936-1954 (Box-folder 1/52)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Sacramento District Council, 1924-1931 (Box-folder 1/53)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, San Diego District Council, 1935 (Box-folder 1/54)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Skagit Valley District Council, 1924-1927 (Box-folder 1/55)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Tacoma District Council, 1923,1935-1947 (Box-folder 1/56)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Texas State Council, 1932 (Box-folder 1/57)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Twin City District Council (Minneapolis - St. Paul), 1929 (Box-folder 1/58)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Vancouver, B.C. District Council, 1928-1937 (Box-folder 1/59)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Washington State Council; Brown, H.H., President, 1964 (Box-folder 1/60)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Washington State Council; Keen, O.D., 5th Vice President, 1919 (Box-folder 1/61)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Washington State Council; Rinke, C.O., 4th Vice President, 1919 (Box-folder 1/62)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Washington State Council; McMurphy, George L., Secretary-Treasurer, 1919 (Box-folder 1/63)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Wayne County, Michigan District Council, 1929 (Box-folder 1/64)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, West Coast Co-ordinating Office; Davis, Kenneth, Coordinator, 1961 (Box-folder 1/65)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Pile Drivers, Bridge, Wharf and Dock Builders, Local 34 (San Francisco), 1934 (Box-folder 1/66)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 36 (Oakland, California), 1925 (Box-folder 1/67)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 112 (Butte), 1924 (Box-folder 1/68)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 131 Part 1, 1923-1926 (Box-folder 1/69)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 131 Part 2, 1927-1930 (Box-folder 1/70)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 131 Part 3, 1930, 1935-1962 (Box-folder 1/71)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 158 (Los Angeles), 1924-1926 (Box-folder 1/72)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 183 (Peoria, Illinois), 1929 (Box-folder 1/73)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 198 (Dallas, Texas), 1926 (Box-folder 1/74)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 231 (Rochester, NY), 1934 (Box-folder 1/75)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 286 (Great Falls, MT), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 1/76)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 313 (Pullman), 1937 (Box-folder 1/77)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 317 (Aberdeen), 1924-1930 (Box-folder 1/78)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Millmen's Local 338 Part 1, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 1/79)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Millmen's Local 338 Part 2, 1929-1936 (Box-folder 1/80)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 426 (Los Angeles), 1929 (Box-folder 1/81)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 452 (Vancouver, B.C.), 1924-1930 (Box-folder 1/82)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 470 (Tacoma), 1924-1935 (Box-folder 1/83)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 483 (San Francisco), 1926 (Box-folder 1/84)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 507 (Nashville, TN), 1936 (Box-folder 1/85)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Ship Caulkers Local 554 (San Francisco), 1937 (Box-folder 1/86)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 530, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 1/87)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 562 (Everett) Part 1, 1926-1948 (Box-folder 1/88)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 562 (Everett) Part 2, 1930, 1932, 1949-1962 (Box-folder 1/89)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 583 (Portland), 1929 (Box-folder 1/90)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 675 (Alhambra, CA), 1923 (Box-folder 1/91)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 701 (Fresno, CA), 1924 (Box-folder 1/92)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 756 (Bellingham), 1927, 1932-1950 (Box-folder 1/93)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 770 (Yakima), 1961 (Box-folder 1/94)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Floor Layers' Union Local 837 Part 1, 1923-1932 (Box-folder 1/95)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Floor Layers' Union Local 837 Part 2, 1932-1937 (Box-folder 1/96)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 944 (San Bernardino, CA), 1936 (Box-folder 1/97)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 971 (Reno, NV), 1923 (Box-folder 1/98)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1011 (Provo, UT), 1923 (Box-folder 1/99)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1065 (Salem, OR), 1929-1933 (Box-folder 1/100)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Millmen's Local 1120 (Portland), 1934 (Box-folder 1/101)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1148 (Olympia), 1922-1937 (Box-folder 1/102)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1164 (Brooklyn, NY), 1924 (Box-folder 1/103)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Shipwrights, Ship Joiners, and Boat Builders Local 1184 Part 1, 1922-1929 (Box-folder 1/104)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Shipwrights, Ship Joiners, and Boat Builders Local 1184 Part 2, 1931-1934 (Box-folder 1/105)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Shipwrights, Ship Joiners, and Boat Builders Local 1184 Part 3, 1934, 1937-1964 (Box-folder 1/106)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1195, 1936-1949 (Box-folder 1/107)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Millmen's Local 1270 (Spokane), 1934 (Box-folder 1/108)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1237 (Aberdeen), 1923 (Box-folder 1/109)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1272 Part 1, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 1/110)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1272 Part 2, 1933-1937 (Box-folder 1/111)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1289 Part 1, 1923-1927 (Box-folder 1/112)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1289 Part 2, 1928, 1936-1954 (Box-folder 1/113)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1296 (San Diego), 1932 (Box-folder 1/114)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1303 (Port Angeles), 1929-1937 (Box-folder 1/115)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1311, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 1/116)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1335, 1923-1934 (Box-folder 1/117)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Wood Shop Caulkers Local 1335 (Wilmington, San Pedro, Long Beach and Vicinity), 1935 (Box-folder 1/118)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1568 (Hollywood, CA), 1929 (Box-folder 1/119)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1583 (Denver, CO), 1936 (Box-folder 1/120)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1597 (Bremerton), 1923, 1935-1949 (Box-folder 1/121)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1644 (Minneapolis), 1923 (Box-folder 1/122)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1651 (Puyallup), 1931-1932 (Box-folder 1/123)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1689 (Tacoma), 1930 (Box-folder 1/124)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1706 (Port Townsend), 1928-1929 (Box-folder 1/125)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1707 (Kelso - Longview), 1923-1931 (Box-folder 1/126)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1708 (Auburn), 1924,1937-1954 (Box-folder 1/127)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1776 (Pendleton, OR), 1923-1933 (Box-folder 1/128)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1780 (Las Vegas, NV), 1938 (Box-folder 1/129)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1799 (Renton), 1924-1934 (Box-folder 1/130)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1849 (Pasco), 1955 (Box-folder 1/131)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1875 (Vancouver, B.C.), 1930 (Box-folder 1/132)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1897 (Paso Robles, CA), 1929 (Box-folder 1/133)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2157 (Hood River, OR), 1926 (Box-folder 1/134)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2205 (Wenatchee), 1930 (Box-folder 1/135)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2207 (Enumclaw), 1928-1935 (Box-folder 1/136)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Pile Drivers and Bridge Builders, Local 2396, 1924, 1935-1954 (Box-folder 1/137)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Pile Drivers, Bridge, Dock and Wharf Builders, Local 2416 (Portland), 1925 (Box-folder 1/138)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2714 (Mount Vernon), 1932 (Box-folder 1/139)
      - Carr, Henry L., 1967 (Box-folder 1/140)
      - Carson, J.O. (Attorney for the Brotherhood), 1940 (Box-folder 1/141)
      - Central Labor Council of Seattle and Vicinity, 1924-1957 (Box-folder 1/142)
      - Citizens Campaign Committee, Charter Amendment No. 1, 1929 (Box-folder 1/143)
      - Coopers International Union, Local 106 (Seattle), 1933-1934 (Box-folder 1/144)
      - Culinary Alliance and Beverage Dispensers, Local 360 (Kelso), 1929 (Box-folder 1/145)
      - De La Mater, Andrew, 1967 (Box-folder 1/146)
      - Dill, Clarence C., 1928-1933 (Box-folder 1/147)
      - United Distillery Workers, Local 19930, 1935 (Box-folder 1/148)
      - Edwards, Frank, 1928 (Box-folder 1/149)
      - Elliot, Lee, Carney and Thomas, 1963 (Box-folder 1/150)
      - Emery, T.P., 1936 (Box-folder 1/151)
      - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers (A.F.L.), 1948 (Box-folder 1/152)
      - Fells, F.W., Business Manager, Firland Sanatorium, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 1/153)
      - Fitzgerald, V.J., 1964 (Box-folder 1/154)
      - Owens, Thomas J., Special Representative, Foster and Kleiser (Division of Metropolitan Broadcasting Corp.), 1962 (Box-folder 1/155)
      - Olson, Oscar, Friends of Soviet Russia, 1931 (Box-folder 1/156)
      - Gibson, H.W., 1923 (Box-folder 1/157)
      - Grand Rapids Store Equipment Corp., 1929 (Box-folder 1/158)
      - Grays Harbor Building Trades Council (A.F.L.), 1928 (Box-folder 1/159)
      - Green, William, 1932 (Box-folder 1/160)
      - Henderson, E.W., 1923 (Box-folder 1/161)
      - Herman E. Schmitt Insurance Agency, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 1/162)
      - Hill, Sam B., 1934-1935 (Box-folder 1/163)
      - Johnson, Roy E., 1954-1959 (Box-folder 1/164)
      - Jones, Wesley L., 1928-1932 (Box-folder 1/165)
      - King-Ramsey-Connor Defense Committee, 1936 (Box-folder 1/166)
      - Odell, Howard; King County Commissioners, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 1/167)
      - Wallace, Scott; King County Commissioners, 1960 (Box-folder 1/168)
      - Wilcox, Ben C.; King County Housing Authority, 1960 (Box-folder 1/169)
      - Branson, William L.; King County Hospital, 1965 (Box-folder 1/170)
      - Sherwood, K.K.; General Superintendent, King County Hospital System, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 1/171)
      - Kramer, John R., 1967 (Box-folder 1/172)
      - Lloyd, Wesley, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 1/173)
      - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (C.I.O.), 1948 (Box-folder 1/174)
      - Lycette, Diamond and Sylvester-- Cisco Construction Co. Case, 1955 (Box-folder 1/175)
      - International Association of Machinists, Hope Lodge No. 79 (Seattle), 1933 (Box-folder 1/176)
      - International Association of Machinists, Auto Mechanics Local 289 (Seattle), 1937 (Box-folder 1/177)
      - Marine Carpenters, Health and Welfare Fund, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 1/178)
      - Miller, John F., 1930 (Box-folder 1/179)
      - Miscellaneous Part 1, 1923-1927 (Box-folder 1/180)
      - Miscellaneous Part 2, 1929-1937 (Box-folder 1/181)
      - Musicians' Association, Local 76 (Seattle), 1928 (Box-folder 1/182)
      - Norway, Vice Consulate, 1927 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Olds. D.D., Secretary to Senator Homer T. Bone, 1933 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Olympia Building Trades Council, 1923 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Pacific Coast Labor Bureau, 1934 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Pacific Roofing Supply, 1948 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Pattern Makers Association (Seattle), 1924 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Pettus, Terry; San Francisco People's World, Northwest Bureau, 1955 (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Plastic Products Corporation, 1957 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - International Association of Plumbers and Steamfitters, Local 32 (Seattle), 1926-1929 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Rawson, Ron L., Ron Rawson, Inc., 1962-1968 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Rosener, Leland S., 1923 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Sailors' Union of the Pacific, 1949 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Schwellenbach, Lewis B., 1935 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Roberge, George W.; Secretary, Seattle Board of Public Works, 1932-1934 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Adams, J.R., Director of Management; Ross, Charles W., Executive Director; Seattle Housing Authority, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Landes, Bertha K.; Mayor of Seattle, 1928 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Roberge, George W., Superintendent of Buildings; Frederickson, Paul, Superintendent of Buildings; Seattle City Department of Buildings, 1928-1934 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Seattle Buildings Trade Council (AFL), 1924-1959 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Seattle Constitution Council, 1934-1952 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Seattle Hardwood Floor Co., 1933-1934 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Seattle Home Modernization Campaign, 1934 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - The Seattle Times, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Single Weaver's District Council, 1942-1949 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Ship and Dock Foremen's Union of Washington, 1952 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Smith, Martin P., 1933 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Staley, Jack, 1933 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Strom and Olsen Hardwood Floors, 1924-1933 (Box-folder 2/27)
      - Joint Council of Teamsters No. 28, 1957 (Box-folder 2/28)
      - Titus, Myron H, Jr., 1933 (Box-folder 2/29)
      - Trinity Methodist Episcopal Church, 1925 (Box-folder 2/30)